I am fancy French Baker who does not
take no foreign answer hello my friend M
suggest some testy desserts for you
today oh no I was looking for something
a little lighter like you know salad no
no no you are in France try the pastry I
really can't do that much sugar no no no
no the sugar in France is Tren and
there's no side effect
whatsoever I guess I can try a bite of
that g the past is live after you get
done with these sugary Delights you're
GNA have such a headache that when you
get to Li Pharmacy you're G to forget to
check your
medication if you do get medicine in
France make sure you check with the
usopc sports medicine team to avoid
chaos like me peoplea France let's get
more pest out here
[Music]